I'm taking the Founder right now!
Eren!
Wait. Could that be him?
Is that Ackermann?
What the hell?
Can't you see I'm a Titan?
Are a bunch of humans
really about to
come and kill me?
No. They're not humans.
They're devils!
Behind us!
Fall back! Take cover!
Shit! I can't shake 'em!
Damn it. We took too long.
The Cart Titan's here.
Pieck!
Made it just in time.
My heavy machine gun armament
is a perfect counter to their ODM gear.
It was worth the time
it took to equip it.
Eren!
It's him. The Beast Titan.
It's Zeke!
Eren Jaeger. I'll kill you!
Kill all of them.
Let none escape.
Stay alive. That's an order.
What the...?
No way. Is that... Mr. Kruger?
No. It's Eren Jaeger.
Damn you!
Wait, Vice Chief Braun!
Hey, it's me!
Vice Chief!
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
He's still alive.
But he's unconscious.
His body should be healing itself
with the Power of the Titans.
At least, as long as
he has the will to... live...
I can't take this anymore.
Please just kill me.
Sit tight, sir. I'll get help.
You know, there're people out there
who aren't enemies.
Udo and Gabi.
Zofia.
All of us are on your side.
Just hang in there. Okay?
Incoming!
That bastard's gonna pay!
Wait! Get back!
I'll kill him here and now!
Good work. Continue to cover
the War Chief's six.
Right!
Just above us!
Bad angle!
Thanks, Galliard!
You saved our butts.
'Preciate the help!
Nice one, Pock!
That was close! Thanks!
Stay on your toes.
I ran into Ackermann a minute ago.
He's still hiding nearby.
This is bad.
Porco! The War Hammer!
Huh?
You formed a crystal shell like Annie's.
It's clearly much harder than my teeth.
But I know that you've spent
the last of your strength.
If you had any left,
you would've used the War Hammer's power
to pierce my neck by now.
You don't have any moves left to play.
Looks like I've outlasted you.
Shit. After all that,
the bastard still has more fight in him?
But if we can take him down,
the Founder's ours.
What are you so worried about, Pock?
Huh?
There isn't any need for us to rush this.
We have control of the battlefield
and its surroundings.
All we need to do now is tighten our net.
The enemy took to the
field wearing ODM gear.
So they have a limited supply
of fuel and ammunition.
In short, they're stranded in
enemy territory with no support.
And the incoming Marleyan reinforcements
have already surrounded the zone,
so there's no escape.
Paradis never stood
a chance against Marley
in a proper war, anyway.
They don't have enough
people or resources.
That's why it's so crucial
we take out the Founder!
Once they lose the power
to start the Rumbling,
they'll be helpless.
It's the ace up their sleeve,
and it's right in front of us!
Which makes it that much more important
that we proceed with caution.
For the time being, at least,
focus on protecting the
War Chief from Ackermann.
Astute as ever, Pieck.
You're exactly right.
I'm not here to fight you, Eren.
I have another opponent.
Let's have our rematch, Levi.
Come on. Show yourself.
You're running out of time, right?
Okay. If there's anyone
who can deal with this mess,
it's War Chief Zeke.
Grice?
Commander Magath! Please
sir, listen! By the stage...
What are you doing?
You haven't been injured, have you?
No. I'm fine!
Then you need to get
the hell out of here.
Sir. Vice Chief Braun
is underground behind the stage.
He's not moving:
It's like he's in a coma.
What happened?
It's my fault. He saved my life.
Who'd he save you from?
It was Eren Jaeger.
Hurry and dock!
We need to reinforce the
troops in Liberio quickly!
I'm told that they're taking
devastating losses there! Huh?
Hey! Can't you see
the fleet around you?
Get that fishing boat outta here!
Hey!
Huh?
Our... ships...
Snap out of it!
Get as far away from here as you can.
But, Commander. What was...
They took out our port.
And only one Titan can...
It looks like they have the Colossal now.
They didn't just kill Bertholdt.
They took his Titan.
Vicious bastards!
It seems they didn't barge in here
without a plan after all!
Give us your worst, you damn devils.
Your plans'll mean jack shit
if I take the Founder
before you can act on them!
Is that the other Ackermann?
Doesn't matter!
War Chief!
They're coming up on our right.
- - Zeke!
- -Get down!
No way...
Pieck! We've got incoming!
What happened?
Hey. Carlo!
Come on, say something! Carlo!
You'll pay for that!
I think it's your turn to pay.
Fire! Hurry!
Pieck!
My men!
Is this... the same view
that you had, Bertholdt?
It must be.
No, please. Don't kill her.
Come on! Finish it!
Don't shoot! Leave Pieck alone!
The shot missed.
What happened?
Did the steam knock it off course?
Or did I hesitate because of that kid?
Pieck!
The Cart Titan's still alive!
Run away...
I can't!
Hurry, Falco.
Keep Pieck covered!
Eat lead, you damn devils!
Hey, Braun! Give Grice a hand!
Understood, sir!
Fall back! Take cover!
This way. Move!
We're dropping like flies.
First War Chief and now Pieck?
Damn it. Damn it!
Damn it!
Damn you!
He's fast. Much faster
than Ymir's Jaw Titan.
So this is the power
of the Jaw. I see.
It's horrible.
Her body can't heal fast enough.
But she has the Power
of the Titans, so why?
The Cart Titan isn't exactly
known for its toughness.
It's not like the Armored Titan.
Wait, where's Reiner?
Is he somewhere close?
You told the Commander
that Eren Jaeger got to him
and knocked him out.
But we can wake him up, right?
I'm not so sure.
He's still underground behind the plaza.
But um... Listen.
I'm sorry, but I feel like maybe
we should let Reiner sit this one out.
What are you saying?
We need Reiner to fight.
To avenge Udo and Zofia
and all the other people
those devils killed.
Hey. Get back here.
Wait, don't go to the windows!
You'll give our location away!
Huh?
Commander!
Commander. I just
spotted the signal lights.
That's a relief.
At least we know that some of the mission
went according to plan.
Whelp. We're counting
on you, Onyankopon.
I've got this, Hange.
Don't worry.
Cross the Internment Zone
at low speed and altitude.
Our troops'll be able to get up
to us with their ODM gear.
We can really only fly through once,
so any stragglers who
miss us are out of luck.
Or in luck, if we get
shot out of the sky.
You came up with one
hell of a reckless plan.
What? You get possessed by
Erwin's ghost or something?
To be honest, I wish I had.
At a time like this,
I could use his strength.
We're dancing on a
knife's edge yet again.
This has to work, 'cause if
we lose Eren and the others,
then we have no future in this world.
Jean. It's here.
Yeah. It's right on time.
Don't tell me they're gonna
try and escape on that thing?
Not happening!
Shit!
What's he...?
H-Hey!
What are you doing?
Stop.
Stop it! Stop it!
Please! Stop!
What just happened...?
The War Hammer Titan got eaten.
And the Jaw Titan is next.
Then they've won.
All our Warriors are finished.
Wait. Not all.
Reiner!
Help us!
Hey.
You have to save Galliard!
He's about to get eaten!
You hear me? Help us!
Reiner!
Shut up.
Just be quiet.
Reiner!
Please. Leave me alone.
- -Help us!
- -Reiner!
Cut it out, you brats!
The enemy soldiers will
hear you! Stop shouting!
Why won't any of you...
just let me... die in peace?
Its strength spent,
the Armored Titan falls.
Furious at the destruction
of her hometown,
Gabi picks up a gun and
sets out to take revenge.
Next episode:
"Assassin's Bullet."